♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ next sunday, a.d. ♪
♪ There was a guy
named joel ♪
♪ not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ he worked
at gizmonic institute ♪
♪ just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ he did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ but his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ so they shot him
into space ♪
♪ we'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
- ♪ the worst we can find ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
- ♪ and we'll monitor his mind ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ now keep in mind
joel can't control ♪
- ♪ where the movies
begin or end ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ to make his robot friends ♪
Let's go.
- Cambot.
- Pan left.
Hi, girl.
What a cool guy.
A wisecracker.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
- ♪ and other science facts ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ then repeat to yourself
"it's just a show ♪
♪ "I should really
just relax ♪
♪ for..." ♪
Ahh.
Ricky, gary,
get me a scotch.
Oh lucy, I wanna
have children.
Aah.
Hi everybody, welcome
to the satellite of love.
I'm joel robinson,
and it looks like
tom servo and crow
are caught
in some kind of
riff-hyper-overdrive
where they're overfascinated
with the idea
of lucille ball
finally meeting up
with harvey fierstein.
- Let's watch.
- Ah, mr. Mooney,
I wanted to meet
robert goulet.
I know what you mean,
harvey.
Love for sale!
See what I gotta live with?
The only way I can get 'em
to interact with me
is take on the mannerisms
of a other
raspy-voiced celebrity.
Uh, sirs, this is...
Brenda vaccaro here, sirs.
Uh, burgess meredith
on line one.
Aah, I'm only taking calls
from david jannsen.
Aah, brenda, darling, postpone
my dinner with kim carnes.
See what I mean?
[Magic voice, raspy]
Commercial sign in five,
four, three, two,
commercial sign now.
[All]
Aah.
I've never met
a real man, aah.
Gary, we need more calgon.
Hey, you guys, hold on.
Hey, hey, hold on.
Gypsy's got an impression
she's been working real hard on.
Oh, ricky,
I wanna be in the show too.
Come on, you guys.
Stop it. Hey, cambot.
Put down the lights.
Gypsy, you ready? Come on.
[Gypsy hums]
- Whoa.
- Aah.
- Uh-huh.
- Did you guys get it?
She's the opening
to the nbc sunday night
mystery movie.
Oh, the mads are calling.
- COOL.
- McCLOUD!
Oh, way to give 'em the razz,
robot critters.
Let's press on, shall we?
Tall and proud.
Our invention this week
are these printers
you wear on the front
of your person.
And tiny diodes
are attached--
tiny, itchy diodes,
you mean.
Tiny diodes are attached
to the headbands,
and they read
your cranial cavity
and reproduce
your self-image
on these
ready-to-wear boards
for all the world to see.
Ready, frank?
Start thinking.
I'll switch on
your computer.
Now, frank, tell our viewers
a little bit about yourself.
Well, when I was
in high school,
I wasn't a freak
or a jock or a brain
or anything like that.
I was basically
one of those people
who got along
with everybody.
I fit in with every group.
I'm basically a good person
with solid goals
and a strong value system.
If I run into someone
on the street,
sure, I'll give 'em
the time of day.
But if they cross me,
they're off my list.
I guess what
I'm trying to say is,
remember me as frank.
One of the good ones.
How'd I do?
Good, real good.
Now I'll turn mine on.
Walk quietly
among other men,
but know their power,
for they are your enemy.
Quietly crush them
as you work diligently
through the night.
Pay attention to
the man behind the curtain,
for he is your ally.
Drink deeply and lustfully
from the foamy draught
of evil.
Uh, do it to the other guy
before he does it to you...
And be bad to the bone,
won't you? Thank you.
Sir, that color
looks good on you.
Oh, this old thing?
I just threw it on.
Well, it's your turn,
joely-oly infantry.
Hey sirs,
that one's pretty neat.
I hope you like mine.
I decided to combine
two popular products.
The kleenex dispenser
and the phone machine.
When I used to live
back down on earth,
when I worked at an office,
everybody complained
that the fax machine paper
was just like tissue,
and that gives me an idea.
And I say, "hey, why not
combine the two?"
So you got a fax machine
kleenex dispenser.
Is it a kleenex dispenser
that thinks it's a fax machine?
Or a fax machine that thinks
it's a kleenex dispenser?
Hey, wait a minute!
Well, thanks, linus.
Send it on up.
I just talked
to dr. Linus pauling,
and he's sending up
the cure for
the common cold.
- Wow!
- Oh, you can
hear it working.
Oh, it's in.
Hey, the cure for
the common cold
is so...
[Joel sneezes]
- Ugh.
- Sorry, sirs.
Gesundheit, snot locker.
Well, your pain
will be complete
after viewing
today's experiment.
Another in a series
of mind-poppingly bad
gamera films.
Today gamera's opponent is--
oh, like it matters.
Chew each bite
32 times, booby.
[Both chuckle]
[Both laugh]
[Both cackle]
- Hey, the--
- oh, we got movie sign!
[Bots, raspy]
Aah!
Hey, come on, you guys.
Oh no, daiei!
[All]
♪ gaos! Gaos! ♪
♪ Daylight come,
and me want go home ♪
Hey, did somebody wipe that with
soap on a window or something?
Oh, that's japanese
for "hideous negativity."
Hidemasa nagata!
Hey, he's an auteur plan.
Did you read andrew sarris's
book about him?
No.
I love planning.
Hmm.
Hey, there's some fumes
coming off your screenplay
there, fumi.
Sounds like maynard ferguson
playing a ballad, doesn't it?
Hey, well,
what does a director do
if all the planning's done?
Mr. Gamera's wardrobe
by botany 500.
Not-so-special effects
by kazufumi fujii.
Oh, gesundheit, tatsuji.
You know, japanese people
make fun of american names.
Oh, I suppose so.
♪♪ [All hum to score]
And the student body of yale
as the townspeople.
Reino in rage and rehab.
Now, are we supposed to be
full-size or miniature?
I can never tell.
[Intercom]
...At gate number three.
So gamera's returned
once again.
After an absence
of nearly two years,
we see again the great beast
of the new state
once called
a benevolent monster.
And the question is,
has it retained its benevolence,
or has it perhaps
changed now?
These are the questions--
HEY, HERE COMES
PAUL McCARTNEY.
Hey.
--And why did it enter into
the very heart of the volcano?
Is it dead now,
or is it replenishing
its energy from the flames?
For the answers,
we shall have to be
patient for a little while.
Until the research party
can return from the scene.
Model, away!
--Is now taking off
by helicopter.
And now I'll sing a medley
of helen reddy songs.
♪ Hello mrs. Fuji ♪
♪ this is harry hosho ♪
♪ can I speak to anyone? ♪
Here we are up on
housing project hill.
[People clamor]
Hmm?
[Phone rings]
Ahh, I knew it would ring.
That's why
I put the camera on it.
- Good planning.
- Mm-hmm.
- Haven't you got him yet?
- I'll keep on trying.
It's hubert humphrey!
"I'm pleased as punch."
I'm tired of excuses.
Whatever happens,
the work on the new expressway
has got to go ahead on schedule.
Apart from the question
of shareholders,
the whole country's
watching to see
if we finish
the road on time.
They're starved
for entertainment.
But I'm tired
of these delays.
There seems to be
one darn thing after the other.
- So what is it now?
Do you know, eh?
- Yes.
- Uh, this darn thing
here, sir.
Oh, that darn thing.
--Uh, it's this section.
All the farmers up there
refuse to sell the land.
We're arguing,
but not getting far.
- Not gettin' far.
- Well really put
the pressure on them.
- Yes.
- Anyway, get them moved out.
- Don't waste any time, eh?
- Yes.
Oh, just a minute.
The chief is calling you.
- What, sitting bull?
- You're through.
Mr. Tsutsumi, the engineer
in charge of the road.
- Now tsutsumi--
- [all] Gesundheit.
I hear that you're having
some trouble with the farmers.
They won't clear off
the land now.
Well, it's part of your job
to make sure they get off.
And get to work moving.
But sir, we've got another
problem on our hands now
apart from the landowners--
the strap in my helmet
broke.
--A report on
the recent eruptions here.
- To hell with the report.
- Ooh.
I don't care about the volcano
or about the monster.
I love you!
Just make sure the farmers
get off the land.
And please don't bother me
with any more of these
- stupid reasons--
- look at the size
of that phone.
Yeah, and another thing.
I don't mind telling you
that you should-- hey!
Hey, hey boss.
What's the boss have to say?
Uh...
- We start work again.
- [Workers] Huh?
Even when there's a chance
there'll be another eruption?
On my face?
Let's get this stuff together
and move on up to this site.
- I'll follow on.
- Okay.
- Right.
Well, I should've
taken that job at honda.
--One thing after the other.
Hang in there, baby.
Friday's coming.
It's walter pidgeon!
I see greer garson
down there.
Really?
Hey, they're flying over
a pot roast.
- Mm.
- Looks delicious.
- Num.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, there's a little pocket
of mint jelly!
Interesting.
Ooh.
Man, the mint jelly's
attacking.
Don't see that often.
I'm amused by
the little pocket of jelly.
Pull over!
There's so many things
to do and see.
Whoo!
Uh-oh.
We thought it would be funny
to split a helicopter
in half.
Hey, my luggage!
Ooh.
Model police, in color!
Geez.
[Men clamor]
What's the buzz?
Tell me what's a-happenin'.
Hey, there must be
a six flags over osaka.
--By mount fuji eruptions.
Was it gamera, perhaps?
I heard somebody reported
a strong green light there.
And what about the party
in the helicopter?
And what of bill
and his love for terry?
Only one thing is certain.
The crash had
nothing at all to do with
the recent eruptions here.
You'll have to wait
for the result of the crash
investigation.
- And gamera?
- Gamera doesn't send out
destructive rays, to the best
of anyone's knowledge.
But still, the possibility
won't be ignored.
Now, that's all I can
tell you at the moment.
Look, I'm a doorman,
leave me alone.
[Men clamor]
Right. I'll go look
for myself.
- D'oh.
- Nobody loves me.
Everybody hates me.
Think I'll go find gaos.
Um, you might wanna
put that helmet on.
Hey, three big macs
for the price of-- oh.
Hey, what is this?
It's the set
of coal miner's daughter.
Is it farmers again?
It says "hollywood."
[Both]
Ooh.
Oh no, it's the cast
of "head injury playhouse."
Oh, watch it.
We wanna trade
lunch money. Now.
[Men grumble]
[Servo grumbles]
Now hold it.
Hey boss, these guys
are out to make trouble.
[Men clamor]
Wait a minute,
let's talk about it now.
Who's supposed
to be in charge here, huh?
Where can I find
the head man?
We're a mob!
We don't need a head man!
Just stop it, all of you!
- Hey...
- What do you think
you're doing?
Who can turn the world on
with her smile?
Him?
You get your men
out of here, quickly.
Well, can I talk
to the head man?
- I'm the head man.
- --Some other time.
At least you can
tell me when, though.
- [All clamor]
- [Bots clamor]
Say...
[Man]
Go on, out of here!
[Servo growls]
Please do what I tell you
and get out quickly.
- [People clamor]
- [Bots clamor]
The biker rally at sturgis
is what this looks like.
Why are all the cute ones
so corporate?
STEVE McQUEEN IS BULLITT.
It's rex dart, eskimo spy.
[Crow mimics banjo]
Hmm.
Wh-- wall drug,
10,000 miles.
- [Cow moos]
- Oh, bless you.
Was he mooing?
What'll happen now?
Ah, you can bet
the construction gang'll
- be back in a few days.
- Look, it's the painters union.
Yeah, we oughta go up
and wreck that site.
- What do you say?
- Yeah, let's go do that.
- Yes. Go ahead.
- Yeah, let's go!
Yeah, let's form
the republic! Whee!
We'll teach 'em.
The more trouble
we make for them,
the more they'll pay us
for our land.
Yes, it's the only chance
we're ever going to get.
We'll make them
pay us more money
than we ever dreamed
of having in our lives.
At least $100.
Just as long as you leave
all the planning to me.
Oh, he's the planner.
Hey, how's that pole
coming, mom?
- You're early.
- I'm not sure that
we're doing the right thing
about this road.
I think it'll bring a lot
of benefits to the village.
- Don't you think?
- Selling one's land
is always
a painful business.
And especially so
if you happen to be a farmer.
- I suppose you're right.
- [Cow moos]
Could somebody milk grandpa?
He's in a lot of pain.
- --Eiichi?
- He's around here.
He was playing outside
a while ago.
Eiichi?
I bought him a new diary
while I was out.
Put your shoes on.
We're at grandma's.
Get your things
up to the site.
Uh-oh. It's the right-wing
highway department death squad.
Let's rape the land!
Come on!
Yeah, I don't think I've ever
met a more greedy crowd
in my whole life
than these villagers.
All this trouble
they're causing is just for
a few more dollars.
What? Buddy hackett
is their foreman?
- Come on, hurry up.
- Okay.
Hey, somebody dropped
their drawers.
- What the hell's happening?
- It's a garage sale.
Look at the mess.
How on earth
could that have happened?
It's perfect. I love it.
I'll tell you what.
This must've happened recently
because it was all right
when we left here yesterday.
Yeah, sometime between
yesterday and right now--
- pretty much.
- Yes, you're right.
This has been done
quite deliberately.
- Mm-hmm.
- No question of an accident.
Excuse me. I'm s-- oh.
All right. If that's
the way they want it,
then they won't stop the road
going through now.
And they're gonna be
the losers in the long run.
So let's get on
with the job.
- Yeah, let's get on.
- Right, let's go.
- Right.
- Okay, right.
Come on. Give a hand
over here.
- Give him a hand, joel.
- Put that box in.
- [Servo mutters]
- Aah! Hey, boss! Hey boss!
Look! Look up there!
- Where?
- Up there, look!
- Oh, I see it.
Well, that wasn't
there yesterday.
What on earth do you think
it could be?
Something that makes us
talk like walter brennan.
Funny smell.
Ah, they're just
smelling themselves.
I remember reading somewhere
gold deposits
sometimes give off
that type of gloss.
- Goldilocks?
- That's right.
Somebody once told me
about that too.
Hey, boss, do you think there
could be gold up there, huh?
- Sure, buttercup, sure.
- Well, it's not impossible--
I see now.
That's the answer, then.
That explains everything.
Those farmers know
all about the gold.
- That's why they--
- thank you, curly joe.
Well, let's go on up
and take a look around there.
We have to make a survey
of the area for the new road.
Bring the stuff along.
We'll go straight up.
Yeah, bring the stuff,
the crap, and the junk.
- Okay.
- And that thing.
And the other thing.
Oh, is bob saget
gonna love this one.
Uh-oh, gamera's homeboy.
- Boy.
- Boy? Crazy boy?
No, it wasn't either.
I'm a guard here.
I'm gonna stop them.
The men from the new road came.
That's what I'm doing.
I see now.
I'm a hiker though.
- And a canadian.
- Do you happen to know
a shortcut
up to the top there?
- You're telling me lies.
- Sweet little lies.
You're not a hiker at all.
You're a newspaper reporter,
aren't you?
I'll be anything
you want me to be.
I knew straightaway
you were a reporter.
- Nice lipstick, kid.
- And I don't think
- I should show you the way.
- Oh, I see.
That's a pity, though.
If I could get a picture
of that green light,
I could still get it
in the evening edition
of any newspaper.
- That would be a scoop, huh?
- I guess it would.
I'd like to see a scoop, too.
But I'm retaining water
right now.
Perhaps we'd see
gamera there too.
And that would be a story.
- Gamera's there?
- Mm-hmm.
Gamera broke my heart once.
But I guess
I still love him.
Maybe gamera can
fix that kid's teeth too.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I just stepped
in something.
Boy, boy.
- Crazy boy.
- Do the big trees
usually fall like this?
Yes, and if no one's around,
does it make a sound?
Die, frog, die!
- Boy. Boy.
- [All] Crazy boy.
Look at that.
Oh, that's just
grandpa's still.
The forest of the trumpets.
...creme de menthe?
Hey. What is it?
- Well, I don't know.
- I'm only six.
Who do you think I am,
carl sagan?
Hey, do all japanese children
have to dress like
fisher price people?
Weebles.
Listen. Isaac stern.
Itzhak perlman?
No, it's yo-yo ma.
My mama was a saint!
No, yo-yo ma. The cellist.
This glow around the cave.
You seen it before?
- No, I haven't.
- Not since the last
monster movie.
There must be
something there.
[Birds caw]
- Hey, stop that.
- You'll go blind.
- What's he doing?
- Hey, hang on.
- Boy.
- [All] Boy, crazy boy.
Why, no. But we may as well
have a look in there
now that we've got this far.
Oh, why didn't
I think of that?
That kid is smart.
What is it?
Mm. It's the cave
of the clan bar.
Hmm?
Sounds like somebody's
leaning on the organ.
Be careful, huh?
Oh, it's one of those
industrial loft type discos.
- That's what it is.
- Oh.
Injun joe? Becky? Huck?
[Squawk]
Oh, flying hell-beasts.
Seen it.
We're having an adventure
just like the goonies,
aren't we?
Huh. The river styx.
Or worse yet,
it's the band styx.
[Roar]
Eh, go see what it is, kid.
I'll wait here.
Probably
the strong wind in here.
Uh, that's me, sorry.
--Another opening somewhere.
- Yeah, an art opening.
- Aah, look at that.
You look at it, I'm bitter.
Oh, it says "abandon hope,
all ye who enter."
Uh, did we come
at a bad time?
- Excuse us.
- Mister!
Mister, help me!
Please! Help me!
I gotta go, kid, I'm sorry.
I got a thing to do with a--
grownups suck. They do.
I hate. I hate
because of them.
Well, tie that yellow coward
round that old oak tree.
Eh, crummy.
Bawk-bawk-bawk bawk-bawk.
Chicken.
What-- my legs!
They're huge!
My feet are swelling!
- What's going on?
- Put me down! Put me down!
Welcome to
this week's edition
of eat the press.
What're we doing in this scene
all of a sudden?
Wait now. Did you hear
something then?
- No.
- Sounded like a reporter
getting eaten.
Hey, boss.
Did you hear anything?
No, not a thing.
Hey.
You don't have to come along
if you're scared.
No, I'll come along too.
I'm not scared.
I do believe in gaos!
I-do-i-do-i-do-i-do
I do! I do!
I do!
Ben! Ben!
Kinda looks like
clint howard.
I don't know
where my friend went,
but there's a pile of poop here
with shoes in it.
Sorry.
[Servo gasps]
What's that?
I'm guessing he's thinking
if he touches that monster,
he's getting a merit badge.
Yep.
Hey, look! Arsenio hall!
Whoop whoop whoop!
I can't believe I'm hiding
behind a dingleberry.
Ooh.
Peekaboo.
[Servo growling]
I see you.
So cute.
This is my neighborhood.
Ooh.
And that'll do it for
the groundbreaking ceremony.
Thank you very much.
- Ooh.
- Ta-da.
Now I've cultivated the ground
to a uniform eight inch depth.
Help me! I'm allergic
to styrofoam rocks!
Hey-hey-hey!
Love to eat kids!
Help me!
Ahh. Pot-stickers.
Mm.
Hmm, too porky.
I'm trying to lower
my cholesterol.
Oh, just the thought of food
makes me sleepy.
[Gamera roars]
Ah! Gamera!
Hey, that kid's a turncoat.
Now he's gamera's pal.
I stick my neck out
for nobody, kid.
He's got the pez jaw
going there.
Every time he screams,
a piece of candy comes out.
Uh, don't get me wrong.
I like you too, gaos. A lot.
Aah!
Look at that.
This is fun! Whee!
Hey look,
it's a shooting range.
Looks like somebody
gave gaos a wedgie.
You guys
ever had a wedgie?
- No.
- In camp once.
I'm coming, darling.
Huh?
My wings are
like a shield of steel.
Hey! Look at the--
hey, let go of my pocket.
Help me!
He's no fay wray, is he?
Oh, we gotta
get out of here.
I gotta laugh.
We do have fun.
Okay, I'm feeling really
artsy-craftsy today.
Kind of captain kangaroony
and a little ray rayner-ish
and foxfire thrown in
just for good measure.
Anyway. I'm gonna
teach you today
how to make today's
star of the film, gaos.
And he's gonna look
just like this when
we're finished.
I guess I'm more of
a hec ramsey fan,
but that's just me.
And I know
you're a big
snoop sisters fan.
Oh, no, actually
I've always loved banacek.
Oh, call it
a guilty pleasure.
Hey-- do you guys mind?
Oh, not at all, joel.
Toss in.
YEAH, BUT LET ME GUESS.
YOU'RE A McMILLAN AND WIFE FAN,
- aren't you?
- You guys are
getting in the way
of my arts and crafts
project.
Oh, well,
joel, you just go on
with your little craftsy-waftsy
holly hobby corner
- and nevermind us chickens.
- [Servo bawks]
Anyway, what you're
gonna need, everyone,
is some scissors
with the rounded edge.
- Use smaller ones.
- [Bots whisper]
Also, paste.
I'm using mucilage
though, today,
because I'm an adult,
and you're not.
And then we'll need an 8x8
perfectly square
piece of paper.
I'm using one that's
a little bigger for clarity.
Now you're also going to need
some powdered rhino horn!
Yeah, and some blood that's from
the murderer's gibbet sweat!
- Right! Ask your mom first.
- Yeah, good one.
Anyway, what you do is
you just take the four corners,
and you fold 'em in,
just like that.
It's simple.
Oh, and while
he's doing that,
you might want to run down
to the public library
and cut out some interesting
pictures from the encyclopedia
to paste on your project.
Yeah, and in case
you're interested,
mucilage tastes
just like sweet honey.
You guys, please do not--
I repeat, do not go down
to the public library
and do not cut pictures
out of the encyclopedia
and do not drink mucilage.
For it does not taste
like sweet honey.
From one who knows.
Okay, then you take--
you turn the whole thing over.
See, I've turned it over--
well, if you get
confused at home,
just draw a little diagram
on your bedroom wall
in permanent marker.
Do not-- I repeat,
do not draw
on your bedroom wall.
You put the four edges in
like this.
- You whip your fingers
in there like this.
- What're you doing?
And you got gaos.
See? Check it out--
and if it doesn't like that,
you're a loser and a failure,
and you'll never
amount to anything.
And you can't do a thing
to change that.
Tom? Tom?
- Tom, can I tell you
something?
- Huh?
You get a time-out
coming, buddy.
No, joel!
Please, I'm just a robot.
[Servo mutters]
Uh-oh, uh, commercial sign.
Joel? Joel?
- Yeah?
- Uh, it's commercial sign.
- Should I get it?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Hey kids. The word for today
is "booger."
Yeah, that's right.
Booger!
Booger-booger-booger
booger-booger-- whah-how!
I don't want any more
clowning around.
- Now you sit down.
- I'm sorry.
- Ow.
- Ew, primordial ooze.
Ooh.
Yeesh.
He's got relief from his monthly
bloating, though, doesn't he?
Okay, okay, rub salt in it,
why don't you?
- Ow! Okay, already!
- We get the point.
Let's change his name
from gaos to "ginsu."
Come on. It takes
a real turtle to cry, gamera.
Let it out!
It's turning into
an artichoke.
It's an oreo cookie.
Ooh.
Now I like gamera!
Ooh boy.
I'd like a bromo, please.
Oh, you had the garlic
cheese puffs, didn't you?
Boo!
Eh, forget agent orange.
I'll show you
how to defoliate a forest.
[Servo chuckles]
Hey, if you can't
stand the heat,
get out of the movie.
Hey look, gamera has
eiichi palms now.
I get it.
Hey, where's that hand been?
Ew. Unfortunate skin.
Oh yeah, eiichi's gonna be safe
on gamera's back, isn't he?
He's got a weak back.
[Servo mutters]
Atomic batteries to power.
Turbines to speed.
Roger. Ready to move out.
I forgot,
I'm a hand puppet.
You know, this high-definition
tv is really something.
[Servo gasps]
Hey!
Get the coleman people
on the phone.
I've got a great idea!
Hey, it's turtle a la king.
Turtle alan king?
A student of the...
I'm tripping, big time.
Ooh.
Okay, here's where
you get off, kenny.
I mean, eiichi.
We've got to do something
now. Get the others.
Hey, what's a guy gotta do
to get a yellow helmet
around here?
Hurry out.
I'm hungry. Let's stop
and get a pizza.
Whee.
Gamera, take me home now.
All right,
the meter's running, kid.
Around the park, please.
Hey, hey, big trouble!
Trouble--
in little china!
You real men can look after
your own troubles.
It's ronald colman!
Come on, let's go!
Eh, excuse me, I just gotta mate
with the tilt-a-whirl there.
Hey, came out of the slot.
It needs a push.
Oh, now they're in
the land of make-believe.
Hi. We're big again now.
What is this,
a chinese fire drill?
I'm just starting to come out
of my shell, I think.
That's what I do.
- Eiichi!
- Kenny! Kenny!
Hi, we got a deal.
I scratch his back,
he scratches mine.
Ooh. You know,
gamera could use
a little exfoliating here.
Got a skin fungus
going down.
- Spider-boy.
- No, frog-boy.
No, he's a tick.
Match on him.
Listen! Don't move!
Okay, move!
[Gamera growls]
The wheel!
They're gonna
invent the wheel!
This-- I thought this was
ferris wheel's day off.
You think gamera likes
being the size of the pentagon?
Don't ever change.
You're beautiful as is.
Stop, stop!
♪ Stop the world,
I want to get off ♪
Servo, I warned you about
doing anthony newley.
- Now stop.
- Okay.
Not you, gamera. The kid.
Now, come on.
Oh, you've gotten heavy.
Right! Take it away.
[Bots hum carnival music]
Like I live to serve you.
I'm outta here.
Jeez, what a gig.
This music is so sad.
Gamera?
I know, I know,
I've got a good heart,
and I love children.
Blah blah blah.
- Someday I'm just gonna...
- [Gamera screams]
Hey, who invited
the elephant?
I guess that's "irrelephant."
- Da-dum.
- That stung.
Here, take the boy.
Yeah, I'll take him.
He's mine. I saw him first.
Hey, he's taking off!
[People clamor]
And as I flew off that day,
I realized I had
become a man.
Thanks a lot, gamera.
Ha-hah,
wave like an idiot, kenny.
I mean "eiichi."
Gah, I can't keep 'em apart.
I know what you mean.
Eiichi, are you
all right, my boy?
Yes I am, I'm fine.
Gamera gave me a ride.
Yeah, well come on.
Tell us all about it.
Tear his coat off, quick!
Hey look. Picnic stick sick.
Ah, bil keane let billy
draw the strip today.
Eiichi's house.
Please hold, thank you.
Eiichi's house, may I help you?
Eiichi's house, hold please.
Gaos is very bad.
He can shoot out a ray.
Yesterday he hurt
gamera's leg with the ray.
It cut him very deep.
Just like a big knife.
I don't believe it.
Suddenly the kid's
an authority on everything.
Mm. Because his voice
sounds like that.
It sounds as if
he screams "gaos."
Now, give me
more licorice sticks.
Dr. Aoki, as a zoologist,
what would you say the beast is?
Well, I'd have to defer
to eiichi on this one.
Would you say it's a bird,
or is it a reptile?
I would like to say. There isn't
any recorded history of it.
Let's just call it
a monster.
I like it. It's snappy.
What about this special ray?
Now, is there any sort of animal
that could produce this ray?
There be
some sort of reason.
Mm. I do have
a little data on this.
Uh, eiichi did
an etch-a-sketch.
Did he just tear his shorts?
...supersonic cutter.
It works through
sound waves oscillating
in the region
of 20,000 cycles.
Well above
the range of humans.
Now here's lucy and viv
at the chocolate factory.
This could be used in surgery
for particular jobs
where a scalpel
would be unsuitable.
A pulsed oscillation
produces the waves.
Then they're beamed
to a metal plate.
- Then kaboom.
- At this stage,
they're quite weak.
So they must be amplified
and more importantly
must be concentrated.
I'll leave
space for laugh here.
And that's the theory.
Once the sound waves
have been amplified,
well, then, they become
a very potent energy.
- Potent.
- Oscillating at
nine million cycles.
They can be used
to a very destructive effect.
- Oops.
- My theory about this is
the monster's rays
are produced the same way.
It's just a theory.
Eiichi, what do you think?
In any case, we have
to proceed from some theory.
And it's the only one
that we have right now.
You're perhaps wondering
about the mechanism
that produces these rays.
- Well--
- I like it!
All the girls will
be wearing it in no time.
- [All shout]
- Ooh. [Whistles]
Now that's scary.
I feel like
I got x-ray specs.
--And then highly amplified
in the other.
- Oh, like quad.
- Mm-hmm.
The neck and the spine
must also be forked.
This is then used
as an oscillator.
- [Servo hums tone]
- Reflected from a plate
in the mouth,
there's your beam.
Then you must be pretty sure
the monster has two throats.
- Who said that?
- Oh yes, I am.
Wouldn't this
tend to restrict
the movement
of the monster's head?
[All]
Sit down. Come on.
It didn't turn its head
while it was being attacked.
Well, that's a weakness
we could use to advantage.
If we could arrange in some way
for it to be distracted,
we could attack it
with safety from the rear.
- Mm-hmm.
- Dr. Aoki, tell me.
What do you think
this green glow is?
Well, I'm only guessing.
A sign of hunger
- or perhaps a sign of rage.
- Or a sign of envy.
This is not especially new
in the animal world.
A number of fish species
have a similar thing, too.
But still,
why should the monster
choose to make
an appearance now?
- Grandpa.
- He must surely
have been hiding somewhere
deep down in
the bowels of the earth
for hundreds
of thousands of years.
- Ick.
- That's right.
- Pull my beard.
- --Undisturbed by
the two recent eruptions.
- Woken from--
- hi, dave.
It could well have been
trapped in some
deep subterranean
air cavity.
But one thing I know.
We must find some way
of destroying it.
It's demonstrated
its viciousness.
It's a vicious gossip.
I hate to think
what would happen if
it chose to attack the city.
- We must get rid of it.
- Good plan.
So please. Arrange
to destroy the beast.
- Yes, I'll do that.
- On my way home.
Right. All the planes are
standing by, sir.
Good. Go ahead.
Roger.
Go ahead.
Calling "a" squadron!
Take off now!
Attack to proceed now!
This is our military?
Oh my god.
Oh. There's
the green glow again.
Oh, marilyn chambers--
I wasn't
supposed to know that.
- It's a pocket
of lung disease.
- Eww.
Wait a minute,
he's making popcorn up there.
[Planes screech]
Random bombing
should do the trick.
Mm-hmm.
I think we should do
a frontal attack first, sir.
Eh, those are the green ridge
mountains up there.
Doing it up, aren't they?
Ahh.
Now, regrettably, there's bound
to be some collateral damage.
Ooh!
Can you imagine
what that thing
could do for cataracts?
Well, that's what
the japanese eye doctor drives.
A cataract.
I said I would stay here.
That was worse
than anthony newley.
- Damn.
- This is great!
Get marketing, pronto!
Yes, sir.
Planes just don't
stand a chance with that.
We'll have to think
of an alternative idea.
This is just plain murder.
I wish gamera would
come back here again.
That's it!
Eiichi, I love you!
Let's get our little tub-ball
an ice cream sundae,
- what do you say?
- He's gone to the bottom
of the sea and stay there
until his leg gets better.
I wish to play
with clay now.
I'm actually a tiny time pill,
you realize.
Gamera! Just hurry up
and get well again, gamera!
And get plenty of rest
and drink plenty of fluids
and take two aspirins.
Gamera!
[Gurgling] Eiichi!
[Gurgling] Kenny!
Oh, you know, you should use
a little peroxide on that.
A little neosporin would do.
Don't pick at it either.
You do not want to do that.
- Hurry up and get well!
- It's hard to resist.
All right, all right!
I'm in the tub!
[Gurgling] Oh, I just love
handel's water music.
[Gurgling] It's so peaceful.
I was fantastic last night.
Hmm?
[Static, feedback]
Hey, the playboy channel.
Eiichi's unscrambling it!
- Sister!
- [All] Sister!
Ugh.
[All]
Wah-wah-wah-waaaaah.
Hoss, little joe!
Hop sing! Hoss! Little joe!
Adam!
You know, wild horses couldn't
drag this plot any further.
--Think everything's
going to be all right?
- Grandpa sounds like a girl.
- I'll go and see.
- Eiichi!
- No, you wait.
- You go to bed.
- Don't want to.
Go on. You must go
straight off to bed now.
Go on, then.
[Gaos roars]
Did you ever see
the last emperor, sister?
Ooh.
Oh.
Hmm?
- Ahh...
- [Servo growls]
There, I just
marked our territory.
--And that one cow.
Where have they all gone to?
We've gotta get some fresh milk
from somewhere.
- Don't look at me.
- --I don't know where
we'll get it at.
Yeah.
- [Gunshots]
- Ooh. Ooh.
I'll kill him!
- I'll kill him!
- Take it easy, take it easy!
- Get the gun.
- Cow cops, in color.
- It's all right now.
- [Man mumbles]
- Take it easy.
- It's all my fault!
It's all my fault!
I'll kill 'em!
When I think about him,
I touch myself.
I do.
He's got a wade sweater on.
I don't know. I guess
he's a little crazy, that's all.
And what do
you two want, eh?
Hey, it's james herriot.
You see, we ran completely out
of food at the site.
We can't buy any anywhere.
And top of that,
my voice is changing.
Looks like you might be able
to sell a bit of milk here.
Well, I can't.
All of my dairy herd
- ran away last night.
- Did they?
But you can't blame that
on us, though.
- It's not our fault.
- Yeah?
Well, he thought it was.
That's right.
That's what he said.
- That's where the...
- He went out all last night.
To try and find the cows.
When he came back again,
he was quite crazy.
And he says that the whole thing
is your fault.
- That's nonsense!
- We haven't touched the cows!
--Since you arrived.
First of all,
we had the volcanoes.
Then we had the monsters.
And all since you arrived.
Now. Get out!
- [Bots strain]
- Hey! Hey!
Everybody in
the village there!
Every farmer
who's lost a cow!
Hey, mrs. O'leary's cow
tipped over the lantern.
Come on! Call the men in!
We need more skin bracer!
Menin.
Let's just forget the milk.
Must you take that
with you everywhere?
- Huh?
- Oh, it's-- oh.
Mom, if the u.N. Calls,
I'm playing with my slot car.
Put your toys away.
Don't you touch them.
They're part of the set.
Now I can't do
the next scene.
Whoo-hoo!
Eiichi, not so loud.
You'll disturb granddad.
Granddad's
already disturbed.
They've been in there
for more than three hours now.
Just saying the same things
over and over.
I swear, this is
the last blanket I'm washing.
--Getting nowhere.
So you think
we ought to wait a while?
Yes, I do.
Well, you know what they say
about animals running away.
- [All cackle]
- --A disaster is coming.
Don't you think
we'd be better off
selling the land now,
while we can?
I'm an old man,
but we've never had
any troubles
like this before.
Not ever since
I can remember.
- Which is last wednesday.
- I know that we'll
lose some money.
But I'm still not sure
we wouldn't be
a lot better off if we took
the company's present offer
for the land and got out?
What about that hired gun
named shane?
Yes, you're right.
I can't get to sleep at night
for worrying about it.
Just waiting
for it to come out.
It's stupid of you
to take this attitude.
- Dig.
- If they know
you're weakening,
well then, they'll just
drive the price even lower.
Wilford brimley?
- No.
- You want to get more money,
don't you?
You want to let the land go
for any less than it's worth?
Do you?
Of course we don't.
It's the right thing to do.
So then, trust me.
Just let me handle
the negotiations for you.
Do you really think we can get
california for us all?
Here's the news.
The monster gaos is causing
great damage
to the mountain provinces.
Up to now, none of the police
nor the armed services--
- hmm?
- Hey, those helmets
are multiplying.
- Oh.
- --Going to report the number
of people are missing.
[Man shouts]
What?
Turn down the radio!
--And police authorities.
Aah! More helmets.
You're leaving
your jobs now?
Yes. May as well.
There's nothing for us
to do here now.
Work on the road stopped
altogether.
And we're worried about
this monster, too.
Hey, looks like
il duce up there.
- The big benito?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, I'm sorry
to see you going.
- Hope you find work.
- Don't forget to call us
when the work stops again,
will you, boss?
- Oh, sure.
- Yeah, right.
Right. Let's go.
All right. If we get work.
Get moving now.
See you guys.
Hey, where's my helmet?
How long do you think we're
gonna have to stay up here?
I'll stay as long as
I'm in charge.
You're in charge
of nothing, pal.
--I'm gonna have to stay.
Hey look, he's got
a pac-man jacket.
Do you two
want to move out now?
Of course not.
Neither of us is afraid
of the monster,
so why should we leave?
[All imitate curly]
He doesn't worry us at all.
[All chuckle]
Is he the catcher
in the rye?
- Sheesh.
- --You, scaring us like that?
- "Scaring us like that?"
- There's nothing
to be scared of.
Why do you say that?
Gaos is a very
ferocious monster.
You mean you ain't scared?
Not at daytime. You see,
he only comes out
in the night time.
I thank the lord
for the night time.
Tell us
how you found that out.
I wrote it down in my diary.
When gaos comes out,
I just write down the time.
Usually right after cheers.
- Mm.
- Oh, I see.
Mitch miller?
It never occurred
to any of us that gaos
might be
a nocturnal beast.
Hiding out during
the daytime,
and coming out at night.
That's right. We never saw even
a glimpse of him
during the bombing attack.
He kept right undercover
the whole time.
In that case, we need only
watch for him at night.
And you can call off your troops
during the daytime, then.
Commander. Don't you have some
special new flares that're
supposed to be practically
as light as daylight?
Yes, we've been
developing some
specially for
anti-guerilla warfare
known as the a.G.I.L.
Flare system.
- ...thing.
- However, they are still
in the trial stage.
Oh, we gotta go.
- Okay.
- Let's try them.
It seems that gaos
is sensitive to light.
- Thanks, dad.
- And if it does seem
that he has
any particular weaknesses,
we must be sure to exploit them.
Okay, now listen, tom.
This is the deus ex machina
which is the god machine.
Okay? In case we can't think of
any way to end the play,
- I'm gonna
lower you down, okay?
- Okay.
And have a big production
ending, all right?
- Roger.
- I can't get into this, joel.
"Ich bin ein monster?"
- What's that
supposed to mean?
- All right.
I just need you
to fake it, okay?
Uh, let's have those
footlights, cambot.
- Ooh.
- Um, welcome
to our production,
which is a combination
of the gotterdammerung
and gamera vs. Gaos.
We call it
the gamera-damera.
Okay? Okay, spuds,
let's really get working now.
Here we go.
♪♪ [Bots fake-trumpet]
Mein...
- Mein lieber schatz--
- oh, we got movie sign!
[Servo groans]
Ouch, that hurt.
Oh boy, that hurt.
Oh. Take that stuff out.
- What a jip.
- Hey.
A thousand points-- I'm gonna
give you the third degree!
- Answer!
- You know what burns my butt?
A flame about that high.
- [Servo chuckles]
- You fool!
I-- I just happen
to be cold, that's all.
You could've fooled me.
[Explosion]
- Aah! It's coming!
- It's coming!
- Aah! Ricky! Aah!
- Take it easy.
There's nothing
to worry about now.
Not with the new flares.
Each one of them's more than
six million candle power.
That's four times brighter
than the moon, when at maximum.
- Neat.
- I'm very glad to hear it.
I only hope it really is
afraid of the light.
Well, does this mean
we can go to sleep now?
[All goofy-laugh]
--Until we've
tested the flares.
You mean we've gotta
sit up all night?
Well, after all, we are
the ones nearest to the hill.
We're supposed
to signal immediately
if we see any sign
of movement here.
- Yeah.
- You sleep first.
And you keep checking
the reports on the radio.
I'll stand up here and keep
throwing things.
You get some sleep now,
okay?
All right. Keep the fire up.
Yes sir, I will.
Now, I'm just gonna
take my picture here. Yeah.
- As a memento.
- You get some sleep.
- Will you be okay?
- Of course I will.
That symbol on his back is
japanese for "I'm with stupid."
- Wait.
- [Radio static]
Oh. That's my favorite
john cage song.
D'oh, would you--
next time, I lead.
You're supposed
to watch here.
I'll get to sleep.
Yeah, see you later, then.
Hey, it's a cheese radio.
No, it's the all orangesicle
station, I think.
Yep. Check it out.
- Hmm.
- Oh man.
I shouldn't've had
that tofu chili.
Yeaah!
- Hey, boss!
- "Free bird!"
- Whoo!
It's coming! Get up!
What? What? What?...
What? What?
Can eiichi come out
and play?
Fire the signal!
I'm your wake-up call!
Yes, we'll be much safer
out here.
[Gaos screams]
- [Man mutters]
- Ooh.
Hey, you might say he's got
a real flare for this.
[All chuckle]
- ♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
- --Fire!
- Open fire!
- Open the window first,
then fire!
Ooh. Boy.
Grace jones
takes one to the head.
- Ouch!
- She can't take it there.
Ha-hah! This is fun!
Model tanks
aren't working, captain.
I'm batman.
Friends, romans, countrymen,
would you let me talk?
[Joel as lugosi]
I vant to drink your blood.
Hey, come on, tokyo.
Give me a hug.
I know you got it in you.
It's gaos buscaglia
here talking.
Oh, I love to laugh!
Long and loud and clear!
He's doing lap folds.
Come on, three more.
Give it to me. Come on.
Feel the burn.
You gotta want it. Go.
- Ooh.
- Oops.
Well, that could've
gone better.
Call me mariah.
[All rasp-voice]
Can't understand it.
Whoa, he's air-surfin'.
[All]
Whoo!
Night on bald mountain.
♪♪ [Servo hums mussorgsky]
- It's moving out.
- To the east side.
- --Moving to the south.
- To a deluxe apartment.
--Central cities
and give them warning!
Tell them,
evacuate where they can!
Quickly. There isn't
much time left.
Thunderbirds are go!
No, tory, no!
[People scream]
Oh-- he spit on the window.
--Hocker.
Hey, a split-level.
Ooh.
Ooh!
Model train to the rescue!
Aren't you glad
you used dial?
Don't you wish
everybody did?
I do.
No, not mister rogers'
neighborhood! No!
Oh...
- It's probably better.
- [Bots] Yeah.
Hmm. Munchy, crunchy,
chocolatey commuters.
Hmm-mm.
Roast 'em, tenderize 'em.
Down they go.
Whoa.
Get me,
I'm david copperfield!
I'm gonna make
this train disappear.
[Servo chuckles]
[People scream]
I got a feeling
about those people.
- Yep.
- Oh, they-- yep.
Never stand in groups,
folks.
Oh, god. Dorito breath.
- Yuck.
- Ooh.
- Sharp teeth.
- Attention, here is
a special emergency
announcement.
Blues brothers,
rhythm and blues review!
--The monster
is known to hate--
ladies and gentlemen,
it's liza!
Ooh, and that's
just to light the patio.
Mm-hmm.
[Man on loudspeaker]
--Is now open.
All citizens
should assemble
at the stadium.
And there are
no fudgesicles left.
Pizza, pizza.
Looks like the dodgers
left brooklyn,
and it's payback time!
Hey, it's helmet day.
It's a german air show.
The monster has disappeared
toward the northeast.
Its whereabouts
are not known.
- Citizens--
- sleep. Sleep!
--Indoors and keep
their lights on.
So that they may be
crushed more readily.
Damn. Where is it now?
We can't go back
without a picture.
Keep going till we see it.
We're probably
wasting our time.
I bet it's miles away
by now.
Hey, who's rockin' the car?
[Passenger shouts]
There it is!
Hurry up! Quick!
- Oh, they're in brooklyn.
- Ahh.
Quick! Get a picture!
Hurry! Quick!
Hey, you took my soul!
Hurry! Now! Hey--
hey, did you guys borrow
this car from allen funt?
Oh, he's still
got a two-door now.
Hurry! Come on!
Let's get out of here!
[Servo wheezes]
[Servo whimpers]
Got half a payment left
on his lease.
Quick!
Thank you. I'd like a dozen
wallet-sized of that, please.
I'll smile.
Ultra-bright smile.
Hey. Gamera.
♪♪ [All hum stadium "charge"]
Starting as second base...
They're gonna settle it
like real men.
On the gridiron!
Yeah.
♪ Patty-cake, patty-cake ♪
♪ baker's turtle ♪
Toro! Toro, turtle!
[All]
Ole!
Oh, sorry. Giant turtle
coming through.
Sorry about that.
Hey you guys, let's do
that cheer we worked out.
[All]
♪ okay gaos, don't be blue ♪
♪ frankenstein was
ugly too! ♪
- [Bots] Whoo!
- He's going again.
Spirit!
Hey, uh,
how does gamera steer?
- I-- got me.
- I don't know.
Ooh. Tragedy struck
at the midway
tilt-a-whirl today.
That's nice.
Cool.
♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
Cold beer! Peanuts!
Gaos programs here!
Frosty malts!
- How does he do that?
- I don't know.
He's tumbling.
Okay.
You know, I bet
the hole in the ozone
is this bird's fault.
[Crow groans]
[Gaos shrieks]
Joel, how does gamera fly?
- I don't know.
- Why is there air?
- Why is the sky blue?
- What's vietnam?
Cheap trick, at buddakan.
Neat.
Uh-oh.
Oh, he's blown a gasket,
and that means
back to the pits for gamera.
- I think gaos is losing--
- gamera's winning!
Hey, somebody
doesn't have a buddy.
Hey, you in the middle,
get a buddy.
[Servo mimics wind]
Uh-oh.
Look guys,
♪ supercar! ♪
[All]
♪ Shovel-head ♪
No, gamera!
Help, mr. Wizard!
Pull up! Pull up!
[All]
Oh!
- He hit the popeye convention!
- How embarrass-king.
[Crow cackles]
Hmm.
Hey, I've got contacts!
Be careful, come on.
Calgon, take me away!
You guys, I swear
I dreamt this last night.
Oh man, we're ramen now!
Game over, man!
Oh, great. Now you've made
the sun god mad.
Good one.
[Gaos shrieks]
I'm the sun god. I'm mad.
Let go! I don't wanna
get my hair wet.
Hey! Look at the monster's--
hey, check it out,
a couple of monsters
going at it. Neat!
There's something you don't see
every day, chauncey.
- What's that?
- Couple of monsters
- going at it.
- Oh.
Mom, he won't let go!
Hey!
Hey, knock it off
down there.
I mean it.
Ugh. Oh.
Got a real toehold on him,
doesn't he?
Oh! Do not feed chicken bones
to your turtle.
Nn-nn.
Oh, I hope that's not
mr. Bubble,
or gamera's gonna get
a kidney infection.
I'm telling you,
he was 3,300 pounds
if he was an ounce!
The one that got away.
[Gamera roars]
It's too hot!
The water's boiling!
Aah!
[Servo gurgles]
- Well, that's it.
Let's go, you guys.
- That's the end.
- That's it.
- ...Oh.
- Darn.
- Jeez, what a night
that was last night.
Yeah, if it hadn't been
for old gamera helping out,
you're right.
Yeah, I lost 50 bucks
on that.
Hey. What's that there?
Hey. Find a penny,
pick it up.
All day long,
we'll have good luck.
Let's go!
Hey, let's go
down to it and look.
What do you say?
Yuck.
It's gaos' foot!
I'll get the sauce.
Should I get the sauce?
Later that same year.
We saw it lying
in the water here.
Yeah, down here!
Come on, quincy,
you gotta help us!
It's over here!
This was
no boating accident!
- --Smaller now.
- Yeah.
It was a lot bigger
before, see?
Oh, I see-- huh?
How could it shrink in size
in half an hour?
No, I swear, it was a lot bigger
when we first saw it.
- Uh-huh.
- You're mad!
No, it's quite true
what he said.
See, it's cold water. Haven't
you men-- oh, never mind.
Sorry.
I tell you, when I first came
across it down by the beach,
it was almost
twice that size.
And that's when I started
talking like georgie jessel.
It might be worthwhile
checking it out anyway.
We might learn something
from it.
And god knows, we need
any information we can get.
Yes, of course, sir.
- Mm-hmm.
Ew, that's probably
his earwax.
Ugh, post-nasal drip.
- Air it out, man.
- Come on in.
Welcome to my home.
It was featured last month in
better homes and gargoyles.
Eww.
- Ugh.
- Big old hangnail
there, huh?
Ow.
I'm going to a different vet
next time.
Ooh, cool.
Hey, I told my mom
I was gonna grow another foot,
and she knit me three socks.
--The next cell type.
Add four.
It's true. You're as impotent
as a dish rag, phil.
Ooh.
Who's making beer?
I smell yeast.
To test an odd theory
that just occurred to me.
- I'm a guy.
- It's worth a try.
Try out
the ultraviolet test.
- Yes.
- Ultraviolet? She's here?
Ultraviolet test?
What's the point?
No point,
just something to do.
--The deciding factor
in attacking the beast.
It does seem unlikely.
But we've got to the stage
where we're willing
to clutch at straws.
Hey, they char-broiled
his foot.
Get the k.C. Masterpiece.
Ooh.
And here comes
the ponderosa heat lamp.
It keeps the jo jo potatoes
warm.
All right. We're ready
to begin the test.
All right. Number two pencils,
and books open.
[Machine whirs]
Hope this doesn't
affect the taste.
Oh no, no, no.
It's cooking unevenly.
They need a micro-go-round.
Ballpark feet.
They shrink when you cook 'em.
They smell like it, too.
Woof.
- Hmm?
- Look.
At what? Oh.
Turn it off.
Gosh, that looks good.
Who wants heel?
I was right.
Pure ultraviolet rays
can eat into tissue.
- I see.
- Ahh.
Well, in that case then,
if the monster
stays out in the sun,
- it must die, huh?
- That's right.
Ooh, he's hard on shoes.
Can't keep this kid
in tennis shoes, I tell ya.
Nn-nn.
[Servo strains]
Oh, and he's never gonna
play piano again.
Look at that.
[Gaos shrieks]
Ahh. Yeah.
Oh yeah, and the-- oop.
[All]
Aah!
I don't believe I did that!
Ow! Boy, did that hurt.
[Crow sighs]
That foot's
never gonna heal.
[Bots]
Nn-nn.
Actually, he's singing
"I feel pretty."
- Oh.
- Yep.
Well, as soon as
the morning sun came up--
- let's go fishing.
- It sort of changed
in its colors.
All its head
went bright red.
Oh, I see.
A sort of danger signal.
Well, it does seem that
the experiment
has proved one thing
conclusively.
And that is, the only way
of killing the beast
is to keep it out
in the sunlight.
Oh, prematurely age it
to death.
But that won't be easy.
Out of sheer
self-preservation,
the monster won't come out
during the daytime.
Wouldn't it be possible
to build an extra-large
ultraviolet-ray projector
and attack it with that?
Man, that guy
thinks on his feet,
- you know that?
- Mm-hmm.
We can never build one
that would be large enough
to be effective.
And even if we could build one,
it would be far too large
to be mobile.
- Mm-hmm.
- The only answer I can see
is lure it out
into the daylight--
and beat the daylights
out of him!
I kid, the daylights.
--Keep it on the run
until after the sun came out.
So that's the way
we ought to be moving now.
There has to be a way.
- Let's think about it.
- Where's eiichi?
--With some plan.
What do you say, chief?
Uh, I, uh, didn't expect
to be called on.
- I don't have anything.
- It's very difficult
yes, it is.
- Eiichi.
- I can come in here,
I rule this place!
Let me go.
You saw gamera fight with gaos.
Is that right?
- Boing.
- Mm-hmm.
- How'd he beat him?
- Tell me, eh?
- You're interrupting
an important meeting,
don't you see?
You're fired!
- I'm sorry--
- can he fire his sister?
Ah, this eiichi here.
He's the one who
rode on gamera's back.
Gamera's a good friend
of his, huh?
He's a real expert
on monsters now.
- You're joking.
- Yes, I am.
Tell me, didn't you get giddy
up on gamera's back?
- Giddy?
- Oh no. Gamera always flies
straight ahead
without turning it off.
That's it!
I could kiss you again!
I mean-- I'm kidding.
Let the record show
I was kidding.
--The answer.
If we could only
keep gaos still
in one place.
And then find some way
of making him dizzy.
- Dizzy?
- [All] Champagne!
All animals'
sense of balance
is governed mainly
by the eardrums.
The inner ear
controls equilibrium.
We lose our balance
when we spin around rapidly.
I'll demonstrate. Whoo...
--Of luring gaos
into a platform.
A pratfall?
--Arrange for the platform
to revolve rapidly.
The monster will be
completely unable to move.
- Hmm.
- Then keep him there
until daylight.
All right, but where could
we get a platform of that size?
There isn't enough time
to build one
of the size that we need.
- I got one in my room!
- --Upstairs, here!
On the roof.
You know, he's right again!
Operation whirlybird
commences now!
Holiday inn,
towering a full
four stories over the city.
The members of
the force ten from navarone
snap into action.
Headquarters.
Sub-station here.
Fireman ability has been
increased by over 300%.
Additional fire can be made
available now.
- Good.
- Got it.
Adam and eve in a raft.
Wreck 'em.
- All right.
- And we need more gloves.
They love their gloves.
Hey, sir,
it's the coffee percolator.
We're gonna get him
really caffeined up
and give him a mean buzz.
That's it.
HEY, IT'S A SWINGIN' 60s
APARTMENT.
Think it'll be
strong enough?
Well, gaos is over
200 feet long.
Must weigh 25 tons.
Well, I wouldn't want him
in the top bunk.
- Mm-mm.
- Good work.
Inform the sub-station men.
Then take the rest
of the day off.
--To stand up
on that thing, huh?
That's a secret
you'll discover later.
Old man!
The control.
It's been reinforced.
All the wiring's
been completed now.
- Got it.
- Get it. Good.
Captain, has all the wiring
been completed yet?
- Yes, sir.
- [All hum]
The president.
Cool wash.
I guess I'll just have
the deli stacker
on the nine grain.
[Crow mutters]
Either my ears are burning,
or someone's ordering lunch.
Oh, they're bringing down
the go-go cage to dance in here?
Watch it. All right.
All right. All right.
- All right.
- Check the flares.
Get ready now.
Get bucky fuller on the line!
We don't know how to finish it!
[Men clamor]
Hey, check--
check on the mic.
Check one, check two. Could
I get some more monitor here?
- Two, two.
- Breaker-niner-one.
- Good, put it in now.
Hey, boss!
Skinny and fatty from
the children's film festival.
I suppose you could
call it a fountain.
- Pete fountain?
- No.
Gaos is known to like
human blood.
- Hey, but who doesn't?
- --Will spray out a substance
which resembles human blood,
both in smell and in taste.
- Who tested it?
- We're hoping it's going
to lure him to the pedestal.
Ugh...
The scientists are
working on how to make
a suitable liquid
in the laboratory.
They're finding it difficult
to get just the right quantity.
So why don't you two
head over there?
Do you think
it'll work out all right?
It's simply got
to work out all right.
- Now back to work.
- Right.
Yeah, I'm sending over
a couple of blood donors.
[Crow cackles]
- The shuttles are ready--
- one cookie
and a cheese dingleberry
and a bounce-around.
Come on, pick it up!
Pick it up!
- Hey, boss-- messenger.
- Right.
It's an army of meter-men.
- Morning!
- Morning! Had your coffee?
Do you have
a minute to spare?
Yes, what is it?
Uh, you see,
we want to withdraw
our previous objection
to the road.
- And submit a new one.
- Do you now?
We want to sell the land now,
at the price you offered.
What do you say?
That all the work on the road
has already been stopped now.
We may change the course.
[Men clamor]
You will have to wait.
I'll tell my boss,
and he'll get in touch with you.
Now I've got this
monster thing to deal with.
All right, let's go.
[Servo grumbles]
And what the devil do you think
you're doing out here?
Hey, you're supposed to be home
milking the cows, old man.
Eh? If you are
weakening now,
you will lose it all.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Just do exactly
what we agreed, huh?
- [Servo grunts]
- Listen, though,
are you quite sure
that we're
doing the right thing?
They say they may even change
the course of the road.
Nonsense. Rumors!
- You'll believe anything.
- Innuendo.
- You leave it to me, will you?
- [Car horn honks]
Hey, can you get the subplot
off the road please?
Come on.
Trying to kill
a monster here.
CONVOY,
STARRING ALI MacGRAW.
All preparations completed.
- All right.
- Okay, you can sit down then.
- I feel so silly.
- Sit down.
All this work to redesign.
I still smell beer.
I don't understand it.
- Dr. Aoki.
- Time for karaoke.
[Servo chuckles]
- Look at this now.
- Yes.
- You've done it.
- It's a baby boy.
All of the qualities
of human blood.
I'm grateful.
I'm grateful!
It's a grape-like beverage.
[All]
♪ 53 bottles of blood
on the wall ♪
♪ 53 bottles of blood ♪
♪ take one down,
write pig on the wall ♪
The wind's blowing in from
the west now. Just about
the right velocity.
I didn't know tennessee tuxedo
was in this movie.
Good. Commander.
Oh, time to go.
- Oh.
- Everything's ideal
- let's do it.
- Let's fall in love.
Set the trap tonight.
I agree. Contact
all operational points.
Right.
And this-- up boy, up!
Come on, boy, come on!
Up! Through the hoop!
Come on, boy! Up!
D'ah, his name
used to be lightning.
Come on, you miserable
son of a-- come on!
Well, um, well,
that's what it looks like
after he jumps
through the hoop.
- Thank you,
ladies and gentlemen.
- [Canned applause]
Thank you. And...
Hey, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Let's keep it going
for tom servo
- and gromit, the wonder dog.
- [Canned applause]
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
We're going to have them back
really, really soon.
A fine, fine performance
by those two youngsters.
And now, before we bring out
our next guest,
I'd like to say hello
to a very, very special lady
here in the audience tonight.
Where is she?
Oh, there she is.
Hi-- hi, everybody.
Thank you, dear. Thank you.
Gypsy's in town this week,
taking over for pat carroll
in gertrude stein,
gertrude stein, gertrude stein.
But now, right here
in our satellite,
a bright young juggler
and magician.
Let's have a big
round of applause
for gaos the great.
Hey! Get the plates.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Number two--
get the next one.
Ow. Ow-ow-ow.
[Servo mutters]
The first one now!
The first-- oh!
Good, get it! Come on.
Ay-- hey!
Ow. Doggone it.
You're losing 'em.
Juggle or something.
Come on.
Come on. Oh--
please, come on. Third one.
Get back to the first one--
[servo mumbles]
- Thank you, thank you.
- And now, for the youngsters,
we have to cut away now for
the youngsters' commercial sign.
You guys are worse than
allen and rossi.
Thank you.
[People clamor]
You told me
you could spin plates.
Well, I thought I could.
You guys should be on
the gong show.
Ooh.
Here we go.
Pull the pressure up higher!
Hey, it's a blood atomizer.
- Hey.
- And I was worried
about frion
wrecking the environment.
Eww.
[Crow aah's]
Hey, he loves running
through the sprinkler.
- Must not be his type.
- Nn-nn.
This is a great view
up here.
- Ooh.
- He's mad 'cause
it's last call.
Whoa!
Look out! Get down!
Get down with it with...
[Gaos shrieks]
Uh-oh.
[Bots mimic plane noises]
Put the pressure on higher!
What, the blood pressure?
Okay, let's face it.
He likes blood,
but not the way you make it.
Ooh.
All right,
it's a last resort,
but send up
the peel-and-eat humans.
Ooh.
Well, it's pretty.
You gotta admit that, don't you?
Aw, that did it.
He's gonna have a facial now.
Mm. I shouldn't really,
but here goes.
- Ew.
- Oh.
I said a "bud light,"
not a "blood light."
Looks more like
tahitian treat.
Ooh.
[Machines whir]
SET IT TO 33 RPMs.
Whoa, either I'm spinning,
or this is some
really good blood here.
- Faster now!
- Right!
Faster!
Did you wanna go faster?
[All]
Whee!
Get the speed higher!
That howard johnson
was designed for speed.
--I'm sure that's safe
for at least three hours.
- So goofy.
- Top speed now!
Operation goofy
now in effect.
It's good, but it's not
as good as blood classic.
- What is it right now?
- Three minutes.
Is he supposed to think
he's taking dance class?
I'm not...
Ooh. Ooh!
- Something wrong.
- Something serious?
We're just gonna die,
that's all.
Oh, well-- oh.
- Ooh.
- Now look!
The power's going.
Nothing like a bloody mary
in the morning.
- How long till sunrise?
- Just one minute.
Tequila sunrise?
Look, the sun's
coming up now.
Ridin' with lady luck!
Oh good, they put him
on a big mechanical bull now.
That'll really screw him up.
You know, he gets violent
when he drinks from that.
Yeah, that blood's going
right to his head.
--Help now.
It must be weakening.
Oh, now look,
he's embarrassed.
Now, if you had a head
shaped like a dixie cup,
- you'd be embarrassed too.
- You got me there.
- What's happening?
- Power's going!
I don't think the sub-station's
gonna hold out!
- We only need five minutes.
- Five minutes!
There isn't any power
coming through at all now!
Wouldn't pay the bill.
- What's up?
- It's gone. It's gone.
Sub-station's burning now!
We'll have to go
to schlotzsky's.
[All]
Finish it! Finish it!
Whoo!
Ah-- aah--
I never liked you!
Come here!
Poor slob, somebody better
call him a sober cab.
Look at him!
Now that's-- that's getting
crushed, isn't it, steve?
We're dead, aren't we?
- That would be us.
- Make a fountain of blood.
I don't believe it...
There he goes again.
Ooh.
...or something.
He must really pit out shirts,
you know?
Yeah, I think so.
[Crow coughs]
Huh. Kinda handy.
Oh, he's gonna get
pulled over for sure.
Yeah.
Uh, honey, could you hand me
that "birds of japan" book?
A flash-bulletin!
The latest of men's efforts
to destroy the monster gaos
have failed miserably.
There seems to be
no way to destroy
this monstrous
and dangerous beast.
The efforts of scientists
have failed,
- and people's hopes
are fading.
- Aww.
My hope is fading.
If only gamera
would come back.
That's it! I could kiss you!
For the third time!
Maybe not.
- [Men clamor]
- Oh, so what is this?
How green is my valley,
all of a sudden?
Oh, eight boxes
of little debbies.
He's too big to get up now.
Has he grown?
- What is it? What is it?
- Headman,
they're not
going to buy the land.
That's right,
and if we hadn't listened
to your stupid advice,
we could've all had money
- in the bank by now.
- Just what are you gonna
do about it?
Wait a minute. I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- I really haven't.
- Don't lie to us!
You knew. Toki went along
to the road corporation
headquarters.
They're changing
the course of the road.
I just don't believe
a word of it!
- It's nonsense, that's what!
- Nonsense!
They're just saying that
to frighten you.
We've listened
long enough to you.
It was your advice
that got us into this.
It's your fault!
It's all your fault!
You'd better think about--
uh, you'd blame me
for the topsoil too.
--Unreasonable about this--
- help us!
- You got the money for us.
We want what's reasonable!
My horses. My cows. My men.
Everything I love.
I've got nothing left.
So what now?
Go away! Go away!
Go away! Go away! Go away!
Eiichi! Stop!
They're just a rotten bunch
of silly stupid--
quick! Get a pencil
under his tongue.
Please, come on now.
It's all right now.
Come inside, honey. Let's
get you some pancake batter.
[Eiichi sobs]
[Servo sobs]
He's very high-strung.
- [Crow clears throat]
- [Servo whistles]
Yep.
I know what
you're all feeling.
I'm very sorry.
But don't blame
my grandfather.
He only did what he thought
was the best thing.
He had to invest in...
So please.
Try to forgive him.
- Okay.
- He wouldn't have
had this happen
for the world.
And you knew that.
- But what about the land?
- Enough.
Come on, let's go.
Ixnay on the and-lay.
Let's go.
[Servo grumbles]
Sumiko.
Shame.
He threw these models
that were in the last scene.
Oh, there goes his
hip socket.
- Uh-oh.
- Ouch.
And then we approached
from the rear,
using the same strategy
we did in normandy.
Now do I tell him
he's not mine?
Oh. Gamera.
Mm.
Gamera wouldn't have any trouble
getting rid of gaos.
He'd just breathe fire on him
and burn him right up.
- Uh-huh.
- And afterwards,
he could come here.
And burn up all those men
who were mean to granddad.
Uh, you're getting into
a weird area here, eiichi.
--But still, there's no way
of getting in touch with gamera.
You only
have to start a fire.
- Start a fire?
- Mm.
Gaos just can't stand fires,
and gamera likes them
more than anything.
He'd soon come.
- Neat.
- You see, gaos would
soon get weak.
Gamera wouldn't have
very much trouble
- beating him then.
- Hmm. Sound. Good logic.
But whereabouts
could we start the fire, huh?
Oh, that wouldn't
be any trouble.
We just set fire
to the mountain.
I like it.
This kid's not half-bad.
This is a great drawing!
This kid draws really well.
--But still,
remember the last time.
He could probably
beat off those flames
with those big wings.
All right, so what if
he did manage to blow out
the first few fires, then?
We'd just keep
lighting new ones.
Always looking on
the bright side, old man.
--You burn down
would be enormous.
It would cost you
millions of yen.
- Yes, I know all that.
- I don't have any yen.
--Think that the gods
sent gaos to punish
all the farmers
for being quite so greedy.
So this is our punishment,
and we get rid of gaos
at the same time.
Perhaps the gods will agree
to forgive us then.
Anyway, if you think
it may well please,
go ahead and set fire
to the whole of the mountain.
Thank you, sir.
I'm grateful.
- No, no, no, no.
- [All] No, no, no, no, no.
...the idea.
He believes that once we get
a big hill fire started,
gamera will arrive on the scene
and finish off gaos.
Now I'm ready for
that piece of cake.
All right then.
Now this may well be
the last chance
we're gonna have.
- So whatever--
- hmm. What flavor?
- This idea has got to work.
- Evergreen?
My men can help you
with this.
They know that countryside.
The logging industry!
Over three billion down!
We work for you
while we work against you!
Feeding you picks
and double-talk.
Stealing your dreams
and selling them back to you!
Why, this tree here
could hold a shamrock shake,
or one of those
bendy cardboard things
in the bottom
of a hostess cupcake.
All right, forward.
Ew. [Servo coughs]
This is neat.
Come on! Bring it on!
What else you got?
He's just blowing out
the flames. Amazing!
Quick! Continue the attack.
Right!
Ooh! Good thing
he has his cup on.
Hey...
[Gaos screams]
Hmm.
I think I hear
the pitter-patter of gamera.
Ah! Gamera.
I'll have my candy now.
Told you he'd come,
didn't I?
Yeah, great. Why don't you
go out and say hi?
♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
Sounds like quo vadis,
not gamera.
You know, I'm intrigued
by this plucky gamera.
[Joel chuckles]
♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
A-ha, so he finally
learned how to duck.
I guess he remembered
he had a shell.
[Bots]
Oh.
That cheeses him off.
Go right behind him,
or he'll burn you to pieces
with the rays, gamera.
Oh yeah. Thanks, eiichi.
I forgot.
Hmm.
No fair.
Boy, you know, I bet
they can never get
those pit stains
out of his shirt.
Whuh-oh. Blindsided.
Oh, cross-check.
He'll be in the box for two.
[Crow growls]
He's down.
- Well, hey.
- Wait-- this is new.
Oh, the flying
head scissors,
- and a figure four!
- Whoo!
- Very impressive.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh-oh. Not again.
You know,
if you bite my leg off,
it'll just grow back.
So don't even bother.
Look. He's getting away.
[All]
Aah, shut up.
Hmm. You know,
you'd be good with curry.
[Servo mumbles]
A little tough.
Uh...
- [Servo spits]
- You got a little...
- Something there.
- Just gotta-- [spits]
There.
Hah! Hah!
I may be a turtle,
but I'm fast!
♪ Dance, dance ♪
♪ do the monster mash ♪
- Huh?
- Hah!
Hah! Can't touch me.
Hmm.
You've got him now, gamera.
Uh-oh, you blew a hose.
Oh, bummer.
♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
- Huh?
- Did we miss something?
Oh.
Here's that mrs. Smith's pie
you ordered.
- Whoo.
- Oh boy, he can impact.
Gamera!
Oh, and again.
Not fair.
Hey, isn't this
how aeschylus died?
- Huh?
- Yeah. Pelican dropped
a turtle on his head.
- Oh.
- It's true, look it up.
And again.
Here's a little gamera
for ya!
Whoo!
Oh, he's lined up well.
Oh, he hit the slot.
He's in the groove--
oh! Perfect game!
He bowled a strike.
- Ow. Owee.
- Oh...
Yuck.
Hey, he's supposed
to be the hero,
and he's getting the snot
kicked out of him.
[Bots]
Literally.
If I could only
reach the rock...
Aah.
- Oh brother.
- Wow.
Come on.
[Joel mumbles]
Oops. Now what?
I don't know,
but I've lost the plot.
Mm-hmm. Me too.
Something must've happened.
I don't know.
Oh, you're a fat old hog,
ain't you?
[Servo squeals]
Sorry.
Uh-oh-- oh, yuck!
Oh, he's spurting
dishwashing liquid.
It's pepto-bismol.
He's got a creamy filling.
Oh, it's everywhere.
I can't watch this.
I've grown to know that
character so well.
Yeah.
Just like when gary died.
Be careful there, gamera!
Hey, no coaching from
the sidelines, shrimp.
Nice day for it.
Red sky morning,
monsters take warning.
Hey, looks like gorbachev.
Yeah, and he's
fighting yeltsin.
Head's turning red!
- You've won, gamera!
- Oh, shut up.
Oh look,
now he's a raku kiln.
Ooh. Cool.
What, suddenly gamera
has a luggage rack?
I guess so.
Oh, he's gotta return
for deposit and recycle.
Oh, that's really sweet.
♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
It's the flying dutchman.
Hmm.
Come on, come on.
No! Don't you do it!
Don't you do it!
I got nowhere else to go!
No-- no, please don't,
not into the volcano!
Please, no! Eiichi, no!
Hmm.
And that's the end of gaos.
Good night,
and may god bless.
Yes. That's the end of him,
all right.
Now it's over, you can start
with the road again, can't you?
Yes. We'll start work
tomorrow.
- Hey, you quit.
- Hey, boss!
Hey, boss! It's you.
Tell everyone to start working
on the road tomorrow.
They're on a new course.
Oh, that was a rumor,
like I told you.
- [All laugh]
- Very gullible.
Good news, boss.
Thank you very much,
for everything.
- You're welcome.
- No, eiichi's the one to thank.
[Joel gasps]
Donuts, peanuts, combo corn,
WALL OF KEYBOARDS, A THOUSAND
DOLLARS' WORTH OF CDs,
crackling pork bread.
Hey.
Come back again soon
and see us, gamera.
Don't forget, now.
Brush!
Eiichi!
- Bye.
- Oh.
- Well, that was fun.
- That was neat--
here are scenes
from next week's gamera.
Oh, what's this?
Well, kids, if you enjoyed
today's movie,
you're sure to like
this shameless padding.
Eh, it's just like
a burt reynolds film.
- These are the outtakes.
- Oh...
Now we can spin him.
Hey...
OH, THIS IS WHERE
DOM DeLUISE BLOWS A LINE.
It kills me every time.
- Remember that?
- Oh yeah, that was
a blast, man.
Really is.
Just a ton of fun.
- Oh.
- [Bots laugh]
- Oh yeah.
- That was great.
This is even better
the second time around.
It's like lasagna.
Now, a lot of people
wrote in and said
they'd like to see
monsters fight.
- Well, here you go.
- Yep.
All you want.
- More than you want.
- Yep, yep yep.
Saw that too.
You know, I'm beginning to think
this is kind of cheap.
Nah.
Oh, I remember this.
This is wh--
wait a minute.
- Now that--
- what's going on?
That's barugon.
It's a gamera family album.
Yeah-- huh?
And here's agnes moorehead.
Looking fine, aggy.
Wait,
they reversed the film.
Remember what
we said about that?
- New combination.
- Yeah, that was funny,
wasn't it?
Aah.
Hey, there's a tick on gam--
- oh, it's eiichi.
- Yep, yep.
And didn't all our eyes get
moist at this poignant moment?
Remember where we were
when we saw that?
[Servo yawns]
Oh, sorry.
- [All cheer]
- Finally.
Act now to get
gamera's funniest moments
and see him on
alan king: Inside
the monster mind.
Oh boy, oh man, joel.
That was about
the lamest attempt
to get rid of a monster
I have ever seen.
Yeah, come on. A fountain
of blood and a turntable?
Sheesh.
Well, you know what?
You guys should snap on
the right side
of your brains.
Come up with some ideas
for how to off gaos.
- That'd be pretty fun.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I got a good one. You could
wait till he goes to the bank,
and then write "I have a gun.
Give me all your money."
On his deposit slip.
Yeah, or, I know, okay?
You ask him to come over,
maybe for, I don't know,
tea or something. Then you
go into the refrigerator
and get out an icicle,
and you off him!
You stab him,
and the evidence melts.
Cool. Cool.
Oh, I got a great one--
- how about--
- oh, I know, I know, I know.
I know, I know.
Uh, you could, um,
chop his head off.
Uh-huh.
Well, where were we?
Oh oh oh, here we go.
You could give him
a cup of gasoline.
- Tell him it's cider,
of course.
- Yes.
Then you make him
eat a wintergreen lifesaver.
'Cause everybody knows
when you bite 'em, they spark.
Then the spark will
set off the gasoline,
- and he'll blow up. Boom!
- Excellent. Okay.
I got an idea.
You invite gaos
to vacation with you
in the bahamas.
And after a leisurely lunch,
you invited him to come out
deep-sea fishing.
And it's your treat,
because that scuba gear
is expensive,
and then you cut his hose.
Yeah! Pretend his head
is a railroad spike,
and drive it
into the ground.
Meh! Bam! With a big hammer.
Yeah. Where were we?
Oh. Okay, okay.
You could get him a job
in a liquor store
in a bad part of town--
hey. You got a better idea?
If you think so, send it to
"ways to snuff gaos"
care of...
Oh, and then you could
beat him to death
with a pork chop
and feed it to the police.
- That's pretty good.
- Yeah!
- That's not half-bad!
We've given it back to you.
What do you think, sirs?
Well, I think you could take
a pair of needle-nose pliers
and jam 'em up into his nose
and twist his septum into...
Uh, well, until next time,
joel-era.
Um. Push the button, frank.
I hope joel picks mine.
I developed a plan
using mucilage
as sweet honey.
Oh.
And I've also come up
with a thing for...
86-ing you, doctor.
Well, frank, that shows
great initiative.
86-- would you
just push the button?